

# Asen Bochukov

● <u>Linkedin Profile</u> ● <u>Location: Sofia, Bulgaria</u> ● <u>Phone</u>: <u>+359899890459</u> ● <u>email: bochukov.asen@gmail.com</u>



**LinkedIn Profile** 

### **Certificates:**



Java8 Oracle
Programmer Certified
Associate



<u>Decipher</u> <u>Programming</u> Certification



Business Acumen
Training Series PwC
2015



Soft Skills Course 2015



Chamber of
Engineers in the
Investment Design



Completed Course Of AutoCad Civil 3D I am Java 8 Oracle Certified Programmer. I am serious, reasonable and reliable person with responsible attitude to work and hunger to learn and grow professionally. During the entire term of my services to all previous organizations, my knowledge, working abilities and techniques have always won the appreciation of my managers.

I am working as a junior Java Developer at <u>Scale Focus</u>. In my current project I am using Spring Boot, Docker Containers, Jenkins, GIT, SQL, Eclipse, Intellij, Gradle, Maven, Scrum methodology and JIRA. The project belongs to our US client, a huge health insurance company.

I have worked as a Survey Programmer at <u>Focus Vision</u>.

I have graduated from the <u>Technological School Electronic Systems</u> associated with Technical University of Sofia, from where I have a diploma for a specialist in electronic computing systems.

My vision is that playing as a team player is the only way to play.

## **Experience:**

### 11.2017-Present

junior Java Developer at Scale Focus

• Main activities and responsibilities

As a junior Java Developer I am working with Spring Boot, Docker Containers, Jenkins, GIT, SQL, Eclipse, Intellij, Gradle, Maven, and JIRA. I have every day Scrum meeting with our US client so we are getting the active tasks aligned for the active sprint and backlog stories groomed for the future sprints.

### 11.2015-12.2016

Survey Programmer at Focus Vision

• Main activities and responsibilities

As a Survey Programmer, I am responsible for programming online surveys, working as part of a client centric team, delivering services to leading market research firms. My job responsibilities include programming and troubleshooting surveys to verify they function according to specifications and standards, following formalized quality assurance and project processes, and maintaining an exceptionally high level of quality for client deliverables. My position involves daily interaction and coordination with internal departments and requires excellent communication skills.

### **Education:**

 $\checkmark$ 

Fresno State

Decipher Programming Certification

✓ Telerik Academy

Student Courses , C#, JavaScript HTML, CSS

✓ <u>Technical school</u> <u>electronic systems - Technical</u> <u>University Sofia</u>

Specialist electronic computing machines

✓ <u>University of</u>
Architecture, Civil Engineering and Geodesy

Engineer – surveyor master's degree

# **Projects:**

- ✓ <u>ElevatorMenu</u>
- ✓ <u>Desktop Calorie</u> <u>Calculator</u>
- ✓ <u>Security Spring MVC</u>

# **Key Skills:**

Always protecting the reputation and interest of the employer.

Working methodically and constantly to achieve the goals!

Experienced in working for International companies!

Experienced in management of a crew!

Sharing the fun with the team!

### 01.2015-08.2015

Student at Telerik Academy

• Main activities and responsibilities

I have been true several courses like C#, JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

### 06.2012-12.2014

Chief Surveyor, 3D CAD Designer at "Globus" Ltd. project "AES"

• Main activities and responsibilities

Organizing and managing surveying crew, working with different software SBG.GEO, Leica, Topcon, LandDesktop and CivilDesign etc., creating digital 3D models.

### 08.2009-01.2011

Chief Surveyor, 3D CAD Designer at

"Kriston engineering"Ltd.

• Main activities and responsibilities

Organizing and managing surveying crew, working with different software Leica, Topcon, LandDesktop and CivilDesign etc., creating digital 3D models.

### 09.2008-01.2011

Surveyor, 3D CAD Designer at "Progeocadengineering"Ltd.

• Main activities and responsibilities

Working with different software Leica, Topcon, LandDesktop and CivilDesign etc., creating digital 3D models.

### 03.2007-05.2008

Surveyor, 3D CAD Designer at "Geotehengineering" Ltd. project "Alpine Bau" Gmbh

• Main activities and responsibilities

Working with different software Leica, Topcon, LandDesktop and CivilDesign etc., creating digital 3D models.

My mission is to become a really good Java software engineer.